AUTO SORT 1.0.0 
LIAM POWELL

WRITTEN IN VISUAL BASIC SCRIPT

CHANGE FILE LOCATIONS TO SUIT YOUR OWN BUILD

ALL LINES ARE COMMENTED FOR COHERENCE

TEST WITH A DUMMY SETUP FOR COMPATABILITY

USE AT YOUR OWN RISK, WHILE NOTHING SHOULD GO WRONG, IT IS NOT GUARANTEED THAT YOUR FILES WILL BE SAVED

INSTRUCTIONS
(No mod to program)
Create folder hierarchy as demonstrated
Anime
	Series
		Genres - WiP
			00-All
Create these folders in E drive
Also Create a folder for every genre you plan on using
Store these folders in the Genres - WiP folder
Create a Genre.txt in every folder that needs sorting
Within this file, type the genre names on seperate lines.
i.e.
	Action
	Drama
	Hentai( ͡° ͜ʖ ͡°)
Run the program titled Auto Sort By Genre

Otherwise feel free to modify folder locations to fit your own needs